[
    {
        "question": "Which movies are based on books written by J.R.R. Tolkien?",
        "genre": "film",
        "answers": ["The Lord of the Rings", "The Hobbit"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the actors that have played the character of Spiderman in movies?",
        "genre": "film",
        "answers": ["Tobey Maguire", "Andrew Garfield", "Tom Holland"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the world's five oceans",
        "genre": "geography",
        "answers": ["Pacific", "Atlantic", "Indian", "Antarctic", "Arctic"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the world's five largest countries by land area",
        "genre": "geography",
        "answers": ["Russia", "Canada", "China", "United States", "Brazil"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which vitamins are considered essential for maintaining good vision?",
        "genre": "health",
        "answers": ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin C", "Vitamin E"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three macronutrients in a balanced diet?",
        "genre": "health",
        "answers": ["Carbohydrates", "Proteins", "Fats"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which 3 fruits are known for having the highest vitamin C content per serving?",
        "genre": "food",
        "answers": ["Kakadu plums", "Acerola cherries", "Rose hips"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the five basic tastes humans can detect?",
        "genre": "food",
        "answers": ["Sweet", "Sour", "Salty", "Bitter", "Umami"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most widely consumed beverage in the world after water?",
        "genre": "food",
        "answers": ["Tea"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three primary colors?",
        "genre": "random",
        "answers": ["Red", "Blue", "Yellow"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planets in our solar system have rings?",
        "genre": "random",
        "answers": ["Saturn", "Jupiter", "Uranus", "Neptune"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which gases are present in Earth's atmosphere?",
        "genre": "science",
        "answers": ["Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Argon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. states border Canada?",
        "genre": "geography",
        "answers": ["Alaska", "Washington", "Montana", "North Dakota", "Minnesota"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which countries are part of the G7?",
        "genre": "geography",
        "answers": ["United States", "Canada", "United Kingdom", "France", "Germany", "Italy", "Japan"]
    }
]
